https://www.releaseteam.com/about-releaseteam/privacy-policy/

updated: May 29, 2019
Privacy PolicyReferences in this Privacy Statement to “ReleaseTEAM,” “we,” “us,” or “our” are references to ReleaseTEAM Inc, a company incorporated in Denver, CO with its registered office at 1400 W 122nd Ave. Westminster, CO. The terms “you” and “your” are references to visitors to the Website and use of our software products. ReleaseTEAM Inc operates the releasteam.com website and offers several software products (the “Product”).This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions.DefinitionsPersonal Data: Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).User Content: User content is content that you create and share while using ReleaseTEAM products.Usage Data: Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated using the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).Cookies: Cookies are small pieces of data stored on a User’s device.Data Controller: Data Controller means a person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal data are, or are to be, processed.For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your data.Data Processor (or Service Providers): Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any person (other than an employee of the Data Controller) who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller.We may use the product of various Service Providers to process your data more effectively.Data Subject” Data Subject is any living individual who is the subject of Personal Data.User: The User is the individual using our Service. The User corresponds to the Data Subject, who is the subject of Personal Data.Information Collection and UseWe collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.Types of Data CollectedPersonal DataWhile using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:Email addressFirst name and last namePhone numberCompany or OrganizationAddress, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, CityCookies and Usage DataWe may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send or by contacting us.Usage DataWe may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our website or when you access the site by or through a mobile device (“Usage Data”).This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g., IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.When you access the Service by or through a mobile device, this Usage Data may include information such as the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser you use, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.Tracking Cookies DataWe use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include a unique anonymous identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.Examples of Cookies we use:Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.Use of DataReleaseTEAM, Inc. uses the collected data for various purposes:To provide and maintain our Service to enable you to create and collaborate on diagramsTo convey updates and changes to your content by others who you have shared your content withTo notify you about changes to our ServiceTo allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do soTo provide customer supportTo gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our ServiceTo monitor the usage of our ServiceTo detect, prevent and address technical issuesTo provide you with news, special offers and general information about other products, product and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such informationRetention of DataReleaseTEAM Inc. will retain your User Content and Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your User Content and Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.ReleaseTEAM Inc. will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.Transfer of DataYour information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.Your data may be processed in the United States, Canada, or any other country ReleaseTEAM or its subsidiaries maintain its facilities.Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.ReleaseTEAM Inc. will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.Disclosure of DataBusiness TransactionIf ReleaseTEAM Inc. is involved in a merger, acquisition, or asset sale, your Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.Legal RequirementsReleaseTEAM Inc. may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:To comply with a legal obligationTo protect and defend the rights or property of ReleaseTEAM Pty. Ltd.To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the ServiceTo protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the publicTo protect against legal liabilitySecurity of DataThe security of your data is important to us, and we take all reasonable commercial measures to ensure the security of your data. We require authentication and verification of your identity via a username and a password or use an established third-party identity product to verify your identity before allowing access to your data. However, do remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Your RightsReleaseTEAM Inc. aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.Whenever made possible, you can update your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to change your Personal Data, please contact us to make the required changes.If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.In certain circumstances, you have the right:To access and receive a copy of the Personal Data we hold about youTo rectify any Personal Data held about you that is inaccurateTo request the deletion of Personal Data held about youYou have the right to data portability for the information you provide to ReleaseTEAM Inc. You can request to obtain a copy of your Personal Data in a commonly used electronic format so that you can manage and move it.Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.Service ProvidersWe may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related product or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.AnalyticsWe may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.Google AnalyticsGoogle Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google product. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its advertising network.For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy Terms web pageBehavioral RemarketingReleaseTEAM Inc. may use remarketing products to advertise on third party websites to you after you visited our Service. We and our third-party vendors use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Service.Google AdWordsGoogle AdWords remarketing service is provided by Google Inc.You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings pageGoogle also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on – https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout – for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy Terms web pageLinks to Other SitesOur Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or product.CommunicationIf you have consented in the registration process, or otherwise, to receive direct marketing material, your personal details will be included in a database compiled for direct marketing purposes. From time to time, you may receive direct marketing information from us relating to our products and product or the products and product of carefully selected third partiesFrom time to time we may send out email messages alerting you that products are available, to remind you about providing feedback or for promotional offers. In addition, you will receive communication from us: 1) if you contact us for a particular reason, 2) to receive your account details, 3) we need to contact you for administrative purposes such as winning a contest, or 4) when we have a substantial change in service or offering. Administrative e-mails will not contain promotional materials. Our Newsletters may also contain promotional materials from creately.com and occasionally from carefully selected third parties. If you wish to opt-out of receiving promotional materials from us, please email us at
info@releaseteam.comChildren’s PrivacyOur Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.Changes to This Privacy PolicyWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.We will let you know via email or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on www.releaseteam.com/privacy-policy
Let's Talk DevOps!Call: (866)-887-0489 Email: info@releaseteam.com
Corporate HQ1400 W 122nd Ave. Suite 202 Denver, CO 80234 720-887-0489 GSA Schedule:
GS-35F-186BA
Massachusetts1257 Worcester Rd. Suite 108 Framingham, MA 01701 866-887-0489
CanadaPMB# 604 1-110 Cumberland St. Toronto, ON M5R 3V5 866-887-0489
SDLC Tools by StageOur PartnersSoftware & LicensingConsulting ServicesSupport ServicesStaff Augmentation & Mentoring
Contact UsBlogCareersNewslettersAbout ReleaseTEAMPrivacy Policy
The SDLC EcosystemOur PartnersSoftware & LicensingConsulting ServicesSupport ServicesStaff Augmentation & Mentoring Contact UsBlogCareersNewslettersAbout ReleaseTEAMPrivacy Policy
